<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InternHunt</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navbar">Navbar</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="terms_and_conditions_text">
        <![CDATA[
            Welcome to InternHunt!<br><br>
            1. <b>Eligibility:</b> Only users who are 18 years or older may apply for internships.<br><br>
            2. <b>Account:</b> Users must provide accurate information. Sharing accounts is prohibited.<br><br>
            3. <b>Application Process:</b> We are not responsible for the selection decisions of companies.<br><br>
            4. <b>Data Privacy:</b> Your data will be used only for internship matching and notifications.<br><br>
            5. <b>Prohibited Conduct:</b> Users must not submit false information or spam companies.<br><br>
            6. <b>Termination:</b> We may suspend or terminate accounts violating our rules.<br><br>
            By using InternHunt, you agree to these terms and conditions.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_text">
        <![CDATA[
            Welcome to InternHunt!<br><br>
            1. <b>Information Collection:</b> We collect information you provide during registration and usage, including name, email, and preferences.<br><br>
            2. <b>Usage of Information:</b> Collected information is used only to match you with relevant internships and send notifications.<br><br>
            3. <b>Data Sharing:</b> We do not share your personal information with third parties without your consent, except for legal requirements.<br><br>
            4. <b>Cookies & Analytics:</b> We may use cookies and analytics to improve the app experience.<br><br>
            5. <b>Security:</b> We implement reasonable measures to protect your data but cannot guarantee complete security.<br><br>
            6. <b>Changes to Policy:</b> We may update this privacy policy from time to time. Continued use of the app indicates acceptance of changes.<br><br>
            By using InternHunt, you agree to this privacy policy.
        ]]>
    </string>



</resources>